Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Academic Files
    - Yale College Student Lunch with President Salovey, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Yale NUS College, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Yale NUS College Advisory Committee Memorandum, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Yale NUS College Budget Monitoring, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Yale NUS College Cash Management and Debt Financing, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Yale NUS College Chong Siak Ching Disclosure, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Yale NUS College Common Curriculum Update, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Yale NUS College Consultative Committee, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Yale NUS College Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Yale NUS College Curriculum Committee Report, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Yale NUS College Educational Resources and Technology Strategic Plan, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Yale NUS College Executive Committee Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Yale NUS College Faculty Advisory Committee Progress Report, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Yale NUS College Faculty Appointments, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Yale NUS College Beyond Age 65, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Yale NUS College Faculty Leave Benefits, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Yale NUS College Film Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Folder 1 of 2, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Folder 2 of 2, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Appointments, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Appointments, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting Folder 1 of 2, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting Folder 2 of 2, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting Folder 1 of 2, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting Folder 2 of 2, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting Folder 1 of 2, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting Folder 2 of 2, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Yale NUS College Governing Board Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Yale NUS College Guidelines for Tenure and Promotion Review, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Yale NUS College Lewis Notes, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Yale NUS College Human Resources Reporting Presentation, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Yale NUS College Media, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Yale NUS College Organizational Chart, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Yale NUS College Presidential Priorities, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Yale NUS College Public Affairs Updates, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Yale NUS College School of Public Health Concurrent Degree Program, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Yale NUS College Staff Update, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Yale NUS College Strategic Plan, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Yale NUS College Student Biographies, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Yale NUS College Study Leave, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Yale NUS College Chor Chua Tan Meeting Notes, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Yale NUS College Topping Out Ceremony, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Yale NUS College Year In Review, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Administration
    - Chief Investment Officer Coal Divestment Steyer, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Chief Investment Officer Endowment Contribution, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Chief Investment Officer Endowment Portfolio, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Chief Investment Officer Fossil Fuel Divestments, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Chief Investment Officer Investments Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Chief Investment Officer Record Hill Wind Project, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Chief Investment Officer Responsible Energy Investment Proposal, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Chief Investment Officer Swensen Celebration, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Facilities Central Campus Utilities Plan, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Facilities Officer Succession Planning, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Facilities Officers' and Deans' Retreat, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Meeting, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Facilities Officers' Program Review Payne Whitney Natatorium Study, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Facilities Officers' Retreat Goals, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - General Counsel Clery Act, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - General Counsel Hong Yen Chang, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - General Counsel Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - General Counsel Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - General Counsel Director Risk Management Search, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - General Counsel Disabilities Straw, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - General Counsel Dreier Appointment Announcement, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - General Counsel Elderkin and Ranpura Correspondence, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - General Counsel Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - General Counsel Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - General Counsel Michigan Department of Environmental Quality Compliance, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - General Counsel Murrey Correspondence, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - General Counsel Peabody and Mohegan, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Robinson Retirement Announcement, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - General Counsel Robinson Retirement Party, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - General Counsel Schmidheiny Honorary Degree Matter, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - General Counsel Schmidheiny Honorary Degree Matter, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - General Counsel Search, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - General Counsel Search, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - General Counsel Search Applicants, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - General Counsel Search Brinkman, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - General Counsel Search Carr, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - General Counsel Search Cederbaum, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - General Counsel Search Cline, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - General Counsel Search Erichsen, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - General Counsel Search Florin, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - General Counsel Search Garfinkel, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - General Counsel Search Livingston, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - General Counsel Search Maldonado, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - General Counsel Search Phillips, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - General Counsel Search Pinkston, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - General Counsel Search Reccomendations, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - General Counsel Search Schwartz, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - General Counsel Tanner Foundation Correspondence, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - General Counsel Tanner Foundation Eisgruber Notes, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - General Counsel Yale-NUS College Issue, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Human Resources Applicants Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Human Resources Applicants Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Human Resources Applicants Lizzotte, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Human Resources Child Abuse and Neglect Policy Announcement, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Human Resources Faculty Satisfaction Survey, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Human Resources Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - General Council Graduate Employees and Students Organization Request, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Human Resources Human Capital Management Presentation, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Human Resources Labor Relations Proto and Kennington Notes, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Human Resources Local 34 Labor Relations, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Human Resources Local 34 Petition, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Human Resources Local 34 Petition, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Human Resources Local 34 Petition Regarding Registrar, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Human Resources Local 34 President Dickess, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Human Resources Local 34 and 35 Invitation, 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Human Resources Local 35 Petition, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Human Resources Long Service Recognition Publication, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Human Resources Long Service Recognition Dinner 25 March, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Human Resources Managerial and Professional Diversity Representation, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Human Resources Officer Talent Reviews Background, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Human Resources President's Award for Staff Excellence Announcement, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Human Resources Retirement Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Human Resources Staff Engagement Campaign Presentation, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Human Resources Transition Peel, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Human Resources Veteran Status and Disability Reporting, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Human Resources Workplace Survey "Advice to New President", 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Human Resources Workplace Survey Results Report, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Human Resources Yale-Labor Relations Progress Presentation, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - New Haven and State Affairs General Assembly Meeting, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - New Haven and State Affairs Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - New Haven and State Affairs Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - New Haven and State Affairs Renaissance of New Haven and the Yale-NH Partnership, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Office of Public Affairs Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - President
      - 43 Hillhouse Chace Notes, c. 2013 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - 43 Hillhouse Director Position Correspondence, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Appointments Deans and Directors Notes, c. 2012 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Barber Retirement Announcement, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence
        - C-Mail (folder 1 of 2), 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 42)
        - C-Mail (folder 2 of 2), 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 43)
        - C-Mail, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 44)
        - C-Mail, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 45)
        - C-Mail Backer, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 46)
        - C-Mail Hamilton, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 47)
        - Compliants, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 48)
        - Condolences, 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 49)
        - Condolences, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 50)
        - Congratulations, 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 51)
        - Correnspondence Congratulations, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 52)
        - Drafts Unsent, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 53)
        - General, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 54)
        - General, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 55)
        - General, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 56)
        - Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 57)
        - Grievances, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 58)
        - Holiday Card from Salovey, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 59)
        - Holiday Cards, 2012-2013 (Box 4, Folder 60)
        - Holiday Cards (folder 1 of 3), 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 61)
        - Holiday Cards (folder 2 of 3), 2013- 2014 (Box 4, Folder 62)
        - Holiday Cards (folder 3 of 3), 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 63)
        - Holiday Cards, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 64)
        - Holiday Cards Mailing Lists, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 65)
        - Invitations, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - Invitations, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Invitations, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 3)
        - Notes, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Office Responsibilities, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - Regrets, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 6)
        - Regrets, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 7)
        - Requests, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - Requests, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - Survey, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 10)
        - Thank Yous, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        - Thank Yous, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - Thank Yous, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        - Thank Yous Books, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        - Thank Yous Books, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 15)
        - Thank yous Gifts, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 16)
        - Web Form Submissions, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 17)
        - Web Site Replies, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 18)
        - Levin Transition Notes, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 19)
        - Moret Biography, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 20)
        - Office Stationery, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 21)
        - Psychology Advisees Underhill, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 22)
        - Salovey Biography, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 23)
        - Salovey Curriculum Vitae, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 24)
        - Salovey presidential Biography, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Speeches
        - Afro-American Cultural Center 45th Anniversary, 2014 October 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
        - AIDS Memorial Project NYC event, 2013 November 20 (Box 5, Folder 27)
        - Alders Reception, 2014 March 24 (Box 5, Folder 28)
        - Alumni Fund Convocation, 2013 November 22 (Box 5, Folder 29)
        - Alumni Lunch, 2014 February 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
        - Amsterdam Video, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 31)
        - School of Architecture Dean's Council, 2013 October 31 (Box 5, Folder 32)
        - Asian Alumni Reunion Update, 2014 April 12 (Box 5, Folder 33)
        - Asian American Studies Conference Reception, 2015 February 27 (Box 5, Folder 34)
        - Asia Development Council Meeting, 2014 March 18 (Box 5, Folder 35)
        - Association of Yale Alumni, 2013 November 22 (Box 5, Folder 36)
        - Association of Yale Alumni Assembly Entrepreneurial Spirit at Yale, 2014 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 37)
        - Association of Yale Alumni Dollhopf and Chapman Talking Points, 2014 December 10 (Box 5, Folder 38)
        - Association of Yale Alumni Governing Board Conversation, 2014 September 6 (Box 5, Folder 39)
        - Association of Yale Alumni Volunteers Summit Update, 2014 April 12 (Box 5, Folder 40)
        - Yale Alumni Service Corp Trip Video Script, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 41)
        - Yale Athletics Brunch, 2014 Aprl 6 (Box 5, Folder 42)
        - Yale Athletics Brunch 1, 2015 April 12 (Box 5, Folder 43)
        - Baccalaureate Address "On Gratitude", 2014 (Box 5, Folder 44)
        - Banco Santander Signing, 2014 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 45)
        - Leslie Woodard Battell Memorial, 2013 October 30 (Box 5, Folder 46)
        - Clifford Beers Gala, 2013 April 27 (Box 5, Folder 47)
        - Blatt Memorial Service, 2014 November 16 (Box 5, Folder 48)
        - Police Leadership Ball, 2013 November 17 (Box 5, Folder 49)
        - Boston Event for Alumni, Parents, and friends, 2013 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 50)
        - Bouchet Leadership Award Dinner, 2014 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 51)
        - Bulldog Days, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 52)
        - California Event for Alumni, Parents and friends, 2013 March 18 (Box 5, Folder 53)
        - Carter Introduction and Discussion, 2014 December 2 (Box 5, Folder 54)
        - Center for Biomedical and Interventional Technologies Hackathon, 2015 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 55)
        - Celebrate Sustainability Keynote, 2013 October 30 (Box 5, Folder 56)
        - Central Party School Senior Government Leadership Program, 2013 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 57)
        - Chicago Event for Alumni, Parents, and friends, 2013 May 8 (Box 5, Folder 58)
        - China All Youth Federation, 2014 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 59)
        - China Lecture Intro (Samantha Power), 2014 December 1 (Box 5, Folder 60)
        - Henry Roe Cloud Gala, 2013 November 9 (Box 5, Folder 61)
        - Class of 1965 Day at Yale, 2014 November 18 (Box 5, Folder 62)
        - Class of 1980 Talking Points, 2015 March 24 (Box 5, Folder 63)
        - Computer Science and School for Engineering and Applied Sciences, 2015 March 26 (Box 5, Folder 64)
        - Computer Science and School for Engineering and Applied Sciences, 2015 March 26 (Box 5, Folder 65)
        - Arthur Vining Davis Foundation Lunch, 2013 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 66)
        - Commencement Address Latin, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 67)
        - Connecticut Camus Compact, 2013 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 68)
        - Robert Dahl Memorial, 2014 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 69)
        - Dean Miller Reception, 2014 May 13 (Box 5, Folder 70)
        - Department of Defense and Yale Tech Exchange, 2014 June 13 (Box 5, Folder 71)
        - Development and Association of Yale Alumni Staff Meeting, 2013 September 10 (Box 5, Folder 72)
        - Development Parent Reception, 2014 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 73)
        - Devoret Birthday Symposium, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 74)
        - Diversity Summit Talking Points, 2014 February 11 (Box 5, Folder 75)
        - Dyslexia and the Achievment Gap, 2013 August 5 (Box 5, Folder 76)
        - East Hampton Event, 2013 August 2 (Box 5, Folder 77)
        - Dr. Ebadi Dinner Toast, 2014 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 78)
        - Jonathan Edwards Reunion, 2014 September 27 (Box 5, Folder 79)
        - Elm-Ivy Lunch, 2014 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 80)
        - Fall Stump 2.0, 2013 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 81)
        - Fall Stump in Greenwich and New York City, 2013 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 82)
        - Fall Stump New York City, 2013 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 83)
        - Family Weekend, 2014 February 8 (Box 5, Folder 84)
        - Football, 2014 November 19 (Box 5, Folder 85)
        - Founders Day, 2014 October 14 (Box 5, Folder 86)
        - Founders Day Drop ins, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 87)
        - Fox Fellowship 25th Anniversary, 2013 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 88)
        - Fox Fellowship 25th Anniversary, 2013 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 89)
        - Freshman Address, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 90)
        - Freshman Assembly, 2013 August 24 (Box 5, Folder 91)
        - Gender Rules Conference, 2014 November 1 (Box 5, Folder 92)
        - Nina Glickson Breakfast, 2014 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 93)
        - Global Health and the Arts, 2013 January 25 (Box 5, Folder 94)
        - Global Health Corps Welcome, 2013 July 17 (Box 5, Folder 95)
        - Globalization 3.0, 2014 July 7 (Box 5, Folder 96)
        - Globalization 3.0 Plenary Session, 2014 July 27 (Box 5, Folder 97)
        - Graduate and Professional Student Senate, 2013 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 98)
        - Graduate School Alumni Association Career Day, 2014 May 12 (Box 5, Folder 99)
        - Graduate School Matriculation, 2013 August 22 (Box 5, Folder 100)
        - Graduate School Matriculation Ceremony, 2014 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 101)
        - Greater New Haven Chamber of Commerce, 2014 April 9 (Box 5, Folder 102)
        - Gruber Cosmology Prize, 2014 October 1 (Box 5, Folder 103)
        - Gruber Foundation Welcome Remarks, 2014 December 1 (Box 5, Folder 104)
        - Gruber Global Constitutional Dinner, 2014 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 105)
        - Gruber Lecture Remarks, 2014 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 106)
        - Habakuk Dedication, 2013 November 18 (Box 5, Folder 107)
        - Halpern Dinner, 2014 January 20 (Box 5, Folder 108)
        - Moulay Hicham Foundation, 2014 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 109)
        - Hong Kong Dinner, 2014 March 17 (Box 5, Folder 110)
        - Hong Kong Event, 2013 April 12 (Box 5, Folder 111)
        - Honorary Degree Acceptance at Shanghai Jiao Tong University, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 112)
        - Hopkins Convocation Speech, 2013 November 11 (Box 5, Folder 113)
        - Human Resources Speech, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 114)
        - Inaugural Address Ideas, Undated (Box 5, Folder 115)
        - Inauguration Volunteer Thank You Party, 2013 December 3 (Box 5, Folder 116)
        - International Parents Welcome Lunch, 2013 August 22 (Box 5, Folder 117)
        - International Parents Welcome Lunch, 2014 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 118)
        - Introduction of Yale's New Provost, 2013 January 14 (Box 5, Folder 119)
        - Jackson Institute Advisory Council Meeting, 2013 April 4 (Box 5, Folder 120)
        - Jewish Museum and Tolerance Center Gala, 2014 February 4 (Box 5, Folder 121)
        - William Lanson Plaza Dedication, 2014 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 122)
        - "Leading Educational Reforms: Empowering Brazil for the 21st Century", 2013 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 123)
        - Aldo Leopold Award (Teresa Heinz), 2014 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 124)
        - M.A. Pravatim Ceremony, 2014 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 125)
        - David Mayhew Conference, 2013 May 29 (Box 5, Folder 126)
        - Yale School of Medicine Reception, 2013 November 4 (Box 5, Folder 127)
        - Mental Health and Wellness Weekend, 2014 April 13 (Box 5, Folder 128)
        - Miller and Pollard Faculty Meeting Remarks, 2014 May 16 (Box 5, Folder 129)
        - Mory's and Yale Club of New Haven, 2013 September 10 (Box 5, Folder 130)
        - Marta Moret Remarks at Parents Leadership Council, 2013 September 29 (Box 5, Folder 131)
        - NAACP Freedom Fund Dinner, 2014 May 15 (Box 5, Folder 132)
        - University National Tsing Hua University, 2014 August 11 (Box 5, Folder 133)
        - Native American Cultural Center Dedication, 2013 November 8 (Box 5, Folder 134)
        - New Haven Promise, 2013 August 7 (Box 5, Folder 135)
        - New Haven Promise Event, 2014 August 14 (Box 5, Folder 136)
        - New Haven Works Ribbon Cutting, 2013 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 137)
        - School of Nursing Ribbon Cutting, 2013 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 138)
        - Nooyi Toast, 2014 May 19 (Box 5, Folder 139)
        - Online Annual Report Video, 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 140)
        - Parents Leadership Council, 2013 February 2 (Box 5, Folder 141)
        - Parents Leadership Council, 2014 February 7 (Box 5, Folder 142)
        - Paris and London Remarks, 2013 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 143)
        - Peck School Graduation, 2014 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 144)
        - Pierson Reunion, 2013 February 16 (Box 5, Folder 145)
        - Tom Pollard Reception, 2014 May 12 (Box 5, Folder 146)
        - Correa Visit, 2014 April 10 (Box 5, Folder 147)
        - President's Award Reception, 2014 November 12 (Box 5, Folder 148)
        - President's Public Service Breakfast, 2014 July 16 (Box 5, Folder 149)
        - Promise Net Lunch, 2014 November 20 (Box 5, Folder 150)
        - Remarks for Town Hall, 2013 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 151)
        - Reunion Update, 2014 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 1)
        - Andrew Carduff Ritchie Lecture, 2014 October 19 (Box 6, Folder 2)
        - Robinson Party Remarks, 2014 October 12 (Box 6, Folder 3)
        - Scripts for Videos to Be Taped, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        - Shanmugaratman Deputy Prime Minister and Yale Ctr for Study of Globalization, 2014 April 14 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - Silicon Valley Alumni Parents and friends, 2013 March 22 (Box 6, Folder 6)